Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Exhibitions
  - Current European Posters, June-Sept. 1955 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - Intaglio Printing, Oct. 1955-Jan. 1956 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary German Book Design, Feb.-March, 1956 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Books, Manuscripts, and Memorabilia, selections from Caxton Club members, April 10-June 8, 1956 (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - Recent European Posters, Sept.-Nov. 1, 1956 (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - Five Centuries of the Printed Bible, Dec.1956-March, 1957 (Box 318, Folder 7-8)
  - Bruce Rogers, April-July, 1957 (Box 319, Folder 1-2)
  - Posters, August-Nov. 1957 (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - W. A. Dwiggins, Dec. 1 1957-March, 1958 (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Business Americana, April-July, 1958 (Box 319, Folder 5-6)
  - Foreign Posters, April-July 31, 1958 (Box 319, Folder 7-8)
  - Famous Chicago Prints, March-June 30, 1959 (Box 319, Folder 9)
  - Publications of American Fine Book Clubs, Feb. 26, 1960 (Box 319, Folder 10)
  - Printing to Instruct and Inspire Printers, June 1960 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Posters, Nov.-Sept. 1960 (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Early Transportation Printing, July 1961 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - The Woodcut and Wood Engraving, 1961 (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - R. Hunter Middleton, Nov. 1974 (Box 320, Folder 5-8)
  - Re-opening of galleries, 1975 (Box 320, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of manufacturing processes, Spring 1975 (Box 321, Folder 1-4)
  - Employee Arts and Crafts, 1975-1976 (Box 321, Folder 5-6)
  - History of the American Magazine, 1976 (Box 321, Folder 7)
  - Flags, 1976 (Box 321, Folder 8)
  - Donnelley is There! 1976 (Box 321, Folder 9)
  - Cliff Feulner, ca. 1975 (Box 321, Folder 10)
  - Photographing the Frontier, Dec 13, 1976-Feb 25, 1977 (Box 321, Folder 11)
  - Printing and the Circus, June-Dec. 5, 1977 (Box 322, Folder 1-3)
  - Marjorie Tomchuk, 1978 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Printed Advertisements in the United States since 1830, 1978 (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - Trees into Paper, Aug. 15-Dec. 10, 1978 (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - Text for mezzanine exhibit, 1992 (Box 322, Folder 7)
  - Gallery photographs, ca. 1930 (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks of exhibition ephemera, 1930-1932 (Box 323, Folder 2-3)
  - Scrapbook of exhibition ephemera, 1930-1935 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - Audubon Bird Prints, broadsides, 1937 (Box 324, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook of exhibits and displays, ca. 1970s (Box 324, Folder 3)
  - Pop-Ups in Advertising, William F. Eisner Museum of Advertising and Design, Intervisual Communications product samples submitted for exhibition, ca. 2002 (Box 324, Folder 4)
- Series VII. Historical Writings and Research
  This series demonstrates RR Donnelley's deliberate efforts to document its own history, and is a rich source of secondary research material and the company's internal analysis of its past. The foundation of this series is the work of Herbert P. Zimmerman, a former RR Donnelley executive who in the mid-twentieth century undertook an extensive study of the company's history. This series contains drafts and typescripts of historical writings by a variety of researchers, as well as primary and secondary source material such as correspondence, publications and photographs. Much of the research and reference material found in this series, particularly in files of the company's early history, consists of photocopies or facsimiles, rather than original material.
  To help distinguish among the many research projects and sources that are included, this series is further divided into nine subseries.
  Subseries 1: Herbert P. Zimmerman, Company History, contains drafts and typescripts of Zimmerman's four-part survey of the company's history from 1864-1927, as well as related correspondence, notes and research material.
  Subseries 2: Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, contains material such as correspondence, publications and photographs relating to the town in which Richard Robert Donnelley was born. An oversize publication from this subseries has been transferred to Subseries 9.
  Subseries 3: Early Business Affiliations, contains documents (primarily facsimiles) that reference early companies in which Richard Robert Donnelley was involved, and individual business associates.
  Subseries 4: Herbert P. Zimmerman, Histories of Customer and Labor Relations, contains drafts, typescripts and research material relating to several of Zimmerman's historical writings. Included in this series is research and writing on major customers of the company, a history of telephone directory printing, and a multi-part history of labor relations.
  Subseries 5: Gaylord Donnelley, Articles for the Donnelley Printer, collects tear sheets and sample issues of the magazine in which Gaylord Donnelley's historical writings were published between 1966-1967.
  Subseries 6: Reuben H. Donnelley Corporation, contains publications, photographs, and promotional material related to the company founded by Reuben H. Donnelley, and particularly its work with telephone directories. Oversize material from this subseries has been transferred to Subseries 9.
  Subseries 7: Personal Recollections, contains dozens of letters, memos, notes, drafts, oral history transcripts, and other documents composed by employees of RR Donnelley, and other individuals closely associated with the company. In these documents, individuals reflect on their careers at the company, memorable events, business accomplishments, and other personal experiences. Many of these documents were composed in response to personal requests from Zimmerman in the process of compiling source material for his book. While many of the individuals represented were executives of the company, this series also includes the recollections of pressmen, engineers, designers, and many others.
  Subseries 8: General Research and Reference Material, includes writings and research files generated through several research projects related to the company's history. This includes additional writings and research files of Herbert P. Zimmerman, as well as material related to an oral history project, undertaken in 1986 at the request of Jack Schwemm. Gaylord Donnelley and Charles Lake worked on this project with Dan Lewis, a graduate student in history at the University of Chicago.
  Subseries 9: Oversize Material and Artifacts, includes material transferred from Subseries 2 and Subseries 6. The descriptive folder headings trace the material to its original location in previous subseries.
  Additional secondary analyses, historical writings and research files are found in other parts of the collection, particularly Series II, IV and IX. Cassette tapes of oral history recordings are found in Series XI.
  - Subseries 1: Herbert P. Zimmerman, Company History
    - Research correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - "Early Donnelley History, 1864-1889," 1958 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - "Donnelley History, 1890-1907," 1958 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - "Donnelley History, 1908-1917," 1959 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1917-1927," 1959 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - "Early Donnelley History, 1864-1889," 1958 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - "Donnelley History, 1890-1907," 1958 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - "Donnelley History, 1908-1917," 1959 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1917-1927," 1959 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - "Early Donnelley History, 1864-1889," 1958 (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - "Donnelley History, 1890-1907," 1958 (Box 325, Folder 11)
    - "Donnelley History, 1908-1917," 1959 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1917-1927," 1959 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - "Review of Early Donnelley History, 1864-1889," 1958 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - "Review of Early Donnelley History, 1890-1901," 1958 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1908-1917," 1959 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1917-1927," 1959 (Box 326, Folder 6-7)
    - "Donnelley and the Telephone Directory," 1955 (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, Crawfordsville," 1960 (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - "Early Donnelley History, 1864-1889," 1958 (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - "Early Donnelley History, 1864-1889," 1958 (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - "Donnelley History, 1908-1917," 1959 (Box 327, Folder 1-2)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1917-1927," 1959 (Box 327, Folder 3-5)
    - "Review of Donnelley History," 1959 (Box 327, Folder 6-7)
  - Subseries 2: Hamilton, Ontario, Canada
    - Photographs of downtown from the Ontario Archives, ca. 1862 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - T.M. Bailey and C.A. Carter, Hamilton, Famous and Fascinating, 1972 (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - Typographical Society, constitution, 1854-1855 (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - William Rosart, research file, 1972-1973 (Box 327, Folder 10)
    - William Rosart, research file, 1972 (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 3: Early Business Affiliations
    - Browne, Francis Fisher (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Electrotype Co. (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Leroy Church (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Church and Goodman, 1863 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Church, Goodman & Cushing, 1862 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - A. J. Cox & Co. Bindery (Box 328, Folder 7)
    - Norman T. Gassette (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - Edward Goodman (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - J. W. Griggs (Box 328, Folder 10)
    - John J. Hand (Box 328, Folder 11)
    - A. T. Loyd (Box 328, Folder 12)
    - P. F. W. Peck (Box 328, Folder 13)
    - H. V. Reed (Box 328, Folder 14)
    - Williams & Donnelley & Co., 1975-1876 (Box 328, Folder 15)
    - Thomas Wilson (Box 328, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 4: Herbert P. Zimmerman, Histories of Customer and Labor Relations
    - "The Story of Life Magazine," 1949 (Box 328, Folder 17)
    - "Surgery, Gynecology and Obstetrics, Clinical Congress of Surgeons of North America, American College of Surgeons, Gorgas Memorial Institute," 1952-1954 (Box 328, Folder 18)
    - "National Bellas Hess, Inc.," 1953 (Box 328, Folder 19)
    - "Great Lakes Register, American Bureau of Shipping," 1953 (Box 328, Folder 20)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1953-1965 (Box 328, Folder 21)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1953-1954 (Box 328, Folder 22)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, research files, 1948-1953 (Box 328, Folder 23)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, research correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 328, Folder 24)
    - Montgomery Ward, 1954 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - "The Montgomery Ward Story," 1954 (Box 329, Folder 2-3)
    - Red Book, Blue Book, and Green Book, 1958 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - "Early Time, Inc.," 1960 (Box 329, Folder 5-6)
    - "Donnelley and the Telephone Directory," Part I, 1886-1906, 1954 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - "Donnelley and the Telephone Directory," Part I, 1886-1906 and Part II, 1906-1916, with supplement, 1956 (Box 329, Folder 8)
    - "Donnelley and the Telephone Directory," Part I, 1886-1906, 1954 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - "Donnelley and the Telephone Directory," Part II, 1906-1916, 1955 (Box 330, Folder 2-5)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1864-1898," 1954 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - "The Feeders' Strike, 1898-1908," 1955 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - "The Feeders' Strike, Supplement, the Bindery Strike, 1898-1908," 1955 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - "Donnelley History, 1890-1907," 1958 (Box 330, Folder 9)
    - "Review of Donnelley History, 1917-1927," 1958 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1898-1908, C. The Compositors' Strike, D., The Photo-Engravers' Strike," 1955 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1898-1908, E. The Pressmen's Strike," 1955 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - "Donnelley History, 1908-1917," 1959 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1908-1933," 1956 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1933-1942," 1957 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, National Labor Relations Board Case," 1957 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, Certification Cases," 1957 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, War Labor Board Case," 1957 (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, Strike and Arbitration," 1957 (Box 331, Folder 10)
    - Drafts, 1955-1957 (Box 331, Folder 11-12)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1864-1898," 1954 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1898-1908, A. The Feeders' Strike, supplement, B. The Bindery Strike," 1955 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1898-1908, C. The Compositors' Strike, E. The Pressmen's Strike," 1955 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1908-1933," 1956 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1933-1942," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, National Labor Relations Board Case," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, Certification Cases," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, War Labor Board Case," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, Strike and Arbitration," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1908-1933," 1956 (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1933-1942," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, National Labor Relations Board Case," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 12)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, Certification Cases," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations, 1942-1947, War Labor Board Case," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - "Donnelley Labor Relations,1942-1947, Strike and Arbitration," 1957 (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Drafts, 1955-1957 (Box 333, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries 5: Gaylord Donnelley, Articles for the Donnelley Printer
    - Copies of articles, 1965-1967 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Donnelley Printer, sample issues, 1965-1967 (Box 333, Folder 5-7)
    - Copies of articles, ca. 1965-1967 (Box 334, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries 6: Reuben H. Donnelley Corporation
    - General, ca. 1910-1993 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, ca. 1928-1963 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Lakeside Press articles, 1919-1930 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Bettye H. Pruitt, "Reuben H. Donnelley, A Centennial History, 1886- 1986," 1985 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Bettye H. Pruitt, interview with Gaylord Donnelley, 1985 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Bettye H. Pruitt, Donnelley and the Yellow Pages, the Birth of An Advertising Medium, photocopy, 1986 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - "This is Donnelley, the Story of the Reuben H. Donnelley Corporation," booklet, undated (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - "The Reuben H. Donnelley Corporation," booklet, 1948 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Promotional booklets, ca. 1950s-1970s (Box 335, Folder 4-5)
    - The Donnelley Manual of Directory Salesmanship, 1934 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Dun and Bradstreet, annual report, 1987 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Company chronology and press releases on company history, ca. 1997 (Box 335, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 7: Personal Recollections
    - Logan Anderson, "What a Salesman Should Know About Donnelley's," 1936 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - "The Lakeside Press, Its Organization and Equipment," 1942 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Frank Johnson, Jr., "The Rotogravure Department," 1942 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - E.D. Chapman, "History of the Evolution of the Personnel Department," 1948 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Stanley Hubbard, "The Story of the Reuben H. Donnelley Corporation," 1948 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Stanley Hubbard, "The Development of the Telephone Directory," 1948 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Stanley Hubbard, "The Story of the Predecessors of the Reuben H. Donnelley Corporation," 1948 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Stanley Hubbard, "The Story of the Origin and the Early Development of the Lakeside Press," 1948 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Stanley Hubbard, "Chronological Development of the R. R. Donnelley and Sons Company," 1948 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Maurice Delworth, history of Rotary Pressroom, 1949 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Bruce A. Young, "History of Department 'D'," 1949 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - H. P. Zimmerman, history of rotogravure, 1950 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Rotogravure, correspondence, 1929 (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - Oliver Cox, "History of the Catalog Department," 1951 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - Howard Close, "Forty Years at Donnelley's," 1952 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - O. Nauman, "History of the Industrial Engineering Division," 1952 (Box 336, Folder 16)
    - William R. Bowes, history of the Efficiency Department, 1952 (Box 336, Folder 17)
    - History and comparison of composing rooms, Chicago, Crawfordsville and Indianapolis, 1917-1953 (Box 336, Folder 18)
    - Herbert Kent, history of the Callahan building, Goldsmith Company and M. A. Donohue accounts, 1953 (Box 336, Folder 19)
    - James Footitt, "Crawfordsville Reminiscences," 1953 (Box 336, Folder 20-21)
    - E.B. Busby, "What the New Plants Mean to Me," undated (Box 336, Folder 22)
    - Maurice Delworth, corrections to Herbert P. Zimmerman's history, 1953 (Box 336, Folder 23)
    - Julio C. Hernandez, "The Lakeside Press, the Largest Printing Company of America," 1945 (Box 336, Folder 24)
    - Oswald Rodrigues Cabral, Terra da Liberdade, Impressoes da America, translation of notes on the Lakeside Press, 1944 (Box 336, Folder 25)
    - Diversification and growth analysis, 1958 (Box 336, Folder 26)
    - Maurice Delworth, "Forty-Four and One Half Years of Letterpress Printing," 1951 (Box 336, Folder 27)
    - Maurice Delworth, "Forty-Four and One Half Years of Letterpress Printing," 1951 (Box 337, Folder 1-3)
    - William R. Bowes, history of printing for the railroad industry, 1926- 1959 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Ruth Steidle, history of the New York office, 1959 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Charlie Singer, history of dictionary printing, 1959 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Oscar R. Daum, "History of the Willard Division," 1963 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Jesse M. Zachary, company history and correspondence, ca. 1966- 1990s (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Bernard G. Lazorchak, "Electronic Graphics Story," ca. 1967 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Edward Busby, memoirs, 1967 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - C.B. McDougal, "Gutenberg to Donnelley," paper read before the Legal Club of Chicago, 1967 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Buck Tones, "The Department 'CC' Story," 1969 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - History of Chicago Department "RE," ca. 1970 (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - Steve Garay, company history, 1974 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - Charles W. Lake, history of the modular plant concept, 1974 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - Charles W. Lake, history of engineering, 1974 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - Arthur Fitzpatrick, correspondence and artwork for T.E. Donnelley's letterhead, 1983 (Box 337, Folder 17)
    - John Horton, memoir of career in the pressroom, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 18)
    - Arthur C. Prine, Jr., "ARTful Letters," collection of correspondence, ca. 1960s-1980s (Box 337, Folder 19)
    - Arthur C. Prine, Jr., "ARTful Letters," collection of correspondence, ca. 1960s-1980s (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Arthur C. Prine, Jr., "Work of Art, a Rather Personal Memoir of My Life at Donnelley," 1988 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Charles W. Lake, history of the technical effort, 1987 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Arthur C. Prine, "R.R.D. Labor History," undated (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Charles W. Lake, history of the production department, 1982 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - John Tankin, "The Rediscovery of the Calumet Plant," 1989 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Dan Hunt, "Early Builders of the Lakeside Press," 1990 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Employee memoirs, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Charlie Rosenfelder, oral history interview transcripts, 1992-1994 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Carl K. Doty, oral history interview transcript, 1994 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Charles W. Lake, Jr., oral history interview transcript, 1994 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Sidney P. Marland, oral history interview transcript, 1994 (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - John (Jack) B. Schwemm, oral history interview transcript, 1994 (Box 338, Folder 13)
    - Jonathan Ward, oral history interview transcript, 1994 (Box 338, Folder 14)
    - Brian Burmeister, Ben Wong, and Paul Lovern, oral history interview transcript, 1994 (Box 338, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 8: General Research and Reference Material
    - References to RR Donnelley and predecessor firms in Chicago directories, photocopied documents, 1880-1919 (Box 338, Folder 16)
    - Changes of company name, photocopied documents (Box 338, Folder 17)
    - Donnelley, Printer, Hamilton, Canada, photocopied documents, 1859 (Box 338, Folder 18)
    - Church, Goodman and Donnelley, photocopied documents (Box 338, Folder 19)
    - Church, Goodman and Donnelley 108-110 Dearborn St., photocopied documents (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Lakeside Publishing and Printing Co., photocopied prospectus, 1870 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Lakeside Publishing Company, photocopied advertisements (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Herbert P. Zimmerman, "Donnelley Publishing," 1952 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Donnelley, Loyd and Co., photocopied documents (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Donnelley, Gassette and Loyd, photocopied documents (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - R.R. Donnelley and Sons, photocopied documents (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Press, photocopied documents 1970-1976 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - List of materials printed by RR Donnelley, 1851-1871 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - List of materials in Memorial Library printed by RR Donnelley, 1864-1871, compiled 1961 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - List of books in Memorial Library printed by RR Donnelley, 1870- 1889 in Memorial Library, compiled 1955 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - List of materials in Memorial Library printed by RR Donnelley, 1872-1889, compiled 1961 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - List of books printed by RR Donnelley from 1890-1900 by customer name, compiled 1958 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - List of books in Memorial Library printed by RR Donnelley, 1890- 1900, compiled 1961 (Box 339, Folder 14)
    - List of books in Memorial Library printed by RR Donnelley prior to 1901, compiled 1952 (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - List of books in Memorial Library printed by RR Donnelley, 1950s (Box 339, Folder 16-17)
    - List of books printed by RR Donnelley from 1900-1907 by customer name, compiled 1958 (Box 339, Folder 18)
    - Listings from customer job index, 1908-1948 (Box 339, Folder 19)
    - Listings from customer job index for independent telephone companies (Box 339, Folder 20)
    - List of Caxton Club titles printed by RR Donnelley, 1896-1955 (Box 339, Folder 21)
    - Early customers, general (Box 339, Folder 22)
    - Early customers, Breeder's Gazette, 1908-1926 (Box 339, Folder 23)
    - Early customers, George T. Brodnax Inc., 1911-1922 (Box 339, Folder 24)
    - Early customers, Chicago History Company, 1886 (Box 339, Folder 25)
    - Early customers, W. B. Clapp & Co., undated (Box 339, Folder 26)
    - Early customers, Farmer's Review, 1882 (Box 339, Folder 27)
    - Early customers, Grand Opera House, 1883 (Box 339, Folder 28)
    - Early customers, Hoopes Brothers and Darlington, 1887 (Box 339, Folder 29)
    - Early customers, W. B. Keen, Cooke and Company, 1875 (Box 339, Folder 30)
    - Early customers, H. F. Kett and Company, 1877 (Box 339, Folder 31)
    - Early customers, Knights Templar, 1879 (Box 339, Folder 32)
    - Early customers, Lake Forest Reporter, undated (Box 339, Folder 33)
    - Early customers, Lewis Institute, 1905 (Box 339, Folder 34)
    - Early customers, Lyon and Healy, 1882 (Box 339, Folder 35)
    - Early customers, Mandel Brothers, 1883 (Box 339, Folder 36)
    - Early customers, McClurg Company, 1873 (Box 339, Folder 37)
    - Early customers, McCormick Harvesting Machine Company, 1883 (Box 339, Folder 38)
    - Early customers, Philipsborn's 1920 (Box 339, Folder 39)
    - Early customers, Random House, 1929 (Box 339, Folder 40)